A Guide to the Andrew Jackson Montague Papers, 1854-1938
Library of Virginia
- VIII: Miscellany., Extent: 1 box. (Box 44)
  - Law notes, grade reports, speech notes, itinerary, and diary--Richmond, Virginia; Brussels, Belgium; and the S. S. Deutschland, 1907-1909. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Senior law class of Richmond, College, honoring A. J. Montague, 20 May 1908. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Muslin banners, 24 1/2" x 36", Montague for Congress,1912. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Recipes, 1913-1916. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Wrapper, McClellan Dineer--out of town reports--Speech of Gov Montague. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Gold painted wrought iron spike. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Gummed labels--A. J. Montague. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Banner-red, white center, two blue stars. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Service certificate for R. L. Montague, U.S. Marine Corps, 21 May 1917-2 September 1919. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Black leather pouch--printed: Danmarks Rigsdag Christiansburg 1920. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Genealogy of Military and Civic Achievement certificate issued to Mrs. Mary Allen Montague, 1 May 1922, Washington D.C. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Honorary doctorate of laws to A. J. Montague from the University of Pennsylvania, 22 February 1923. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Biographical and genealogical sketches. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Claim of C. J. Campbell for an attorney's fee, endorsed by H. D. Flood, Claude Swanson, and Thomas Staples Martin. (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Notes and transcripts on French Spoliation Claims. (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Mr. Hull's draft on Paris pact. (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Notes. (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Red and blue silk ribbons. (Box 45, Folder 25)
- IX: Photographs., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 46-47)
  Pictures contain postcards, reproductions of paintings, and photographs of Montague, family members, and others.
  - Constantinople (Istanbul, Turkey). (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Budapest, Hungary, postcards, 1915. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Berlin in Original Photographien, Berlin, Germany. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - København Og Omegn, a picture album of Copenhaven, Denmark. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Prague, Czechoslovakia, photoprints. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Postcards of scenes in Paris, France, 1929. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Page pamphlets on Bucharest Notes Historiques Et Estampes de Georges Olszewski, Bucharest, Romania, 1929. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Bucuresti, Bucharest, Romania, picture album. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Glendalough, County Wicklow, Ireland, postcards, [1930]. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Cartoon of the the 27th Conference of the Interparliamentary Union, 1931. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Postcards of Athens, Greece. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Panorama de la bataile de l'yser, [Panorama of the battle of Ypres], Brussels, Belgium. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Bucharest, Romania, postcards. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Köln a. Rhein, [Cologne, Germany, on the Rhine]. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Cathedral at Cologne, Germany, print and postcards. (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Postcards of views of the Rhine, Cologne, Germany. (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Postcards of Constantinople [Istanbul, Turkey]. (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Postcards of Geneva, Switzerland. (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Postcards of London, England. (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Postcards of the Restaurant Turquoise. (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Prints of Stockholm, Sweden. (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Photograph of sculptured classical figures. (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Postcards and stickers of Venice, Italy. (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Print of Monterey Peninsula, California. (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Postcards of Michigan. (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Postcards of Kinsale, Virginia. (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Postcards of the Lee family of Virginia. (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Print of Mount Vernon [Fairfax County, Virginia]. (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Print of the Sir Christopher Wren building at the College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Virginia. (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Print of the Thomas Nelson House, Yorktown, Virginia. (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Print of the Lincoln Memorial. (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Prints of classical figures. (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Prints of unknown individuals. (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Reproductions of paintings of Madonna and Child by Holbein, Ruebens, Van Dyke, adn Aldorffer. (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Photograph of Charles Chandler, 1911. (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Photograph of Herbert Hoover, wife, and others. (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - Photograph of Herbert Hoover and group of Army and Navy officers. (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Photograph of Willina[?] McCaskie, 1917. (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - Photograph of Allen Fairfax Montague, ca. 1918. (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Photograph of A. J. Montague and unidentified group. (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - Photographs from the Pan-American Conference in Brazil, 1906. (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - Family gathering[?] at Maplewood Farm, 1912. (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - Photograph of the Interparliamentary Union[?], [1921?]. (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - Photograph of the Interparliamentary Union, Geneva, Switzerland, 1922. (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - Photograph of the Interparliamentary Union, Paris, France, 1927. (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Photograph of the Interparliamentary Union, Berlin, Germany, 1928. (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - Photographs of the Interparliamentary Union, Bucharest, Romania, 1931. (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Photographs of Andrew Jackson Montague. (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - Photographs of A. J. Montague and grandchildren. (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Photo-engraving plate of Andrew Jackson Montague. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of A. J. Montague in Europe. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of A. J. and Elizabeth Bessie Montague. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of A. J. Montague. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Mrs. Elizabeth Bessie Montague. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Photograph of Edgar Burwell Montague, ca. 1918. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Photograph of John Tyler Montague, ca. 1918. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of Louis Latané Montague, 1918. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Robert Latané Montague, ca. 1917-1930. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Photograph of Lieutenant Erik Nelson and Lieutenant John Harding during 1st round the world flight, 16 April-28 September 1924. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Photograph of Ella Schildkraut, 1931. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Photograph of Adele C. Scott, 1920. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Photograph of Governor Henry C. Stuart with unidentified group in Washington D.C., ca. 1916. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of the Home for Needy Confederate Women. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Photograph of the Robert E. Lee Monument, Richmond, Virginia. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Photograph of unidentified house. (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of unidentied individuals. (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Print of the Virginia State Capitol, Richmond, Virginia. (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Photograph of the George Washington statue in the Virginia State Capitol. (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Photograph of banquet, Women's Organization for National Prohibition Reform, Mayflower Hotel, Washington D.C., 12 April 1932. (Box 47, Folder 20)
- X: Printed Materials, 1842-1937., Extent: 14. (Box 48-61)
  Printed Materials, 1842-1937, contain published pamphlets and articles concerning a wide range of topics, including Virginia politics and history; American politics and history; prominent Virginians and Americans; education; genealogy, and other topics.
  - An Address Delivered Before the Society of the Alumni of William and Mary College, upon the 5th of July, 1842 by Beverly Tucker, 1842. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - A Discourse on the Death of General Washington, Late President of the United States: Delivered on the 22nd of February, 1800, in the Church in Williamsburg by James Madison, 1844, fourth edition. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Conscience and the Constitution with Remarks on the Recent Speech of the Hon. Daniel Webster on the Subject of Slavery by M. Stuart, 1850. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Address Delivered before the Literary Societies of the University of Virginia, on the 28th June, 1855 by M. F. Maury, 1855. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - The New Constitution of Virginia with the amended Bil of Rights as adopted by the Reform Convention of 1850-'51, 1859. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Discourse on the Life and Character of George Peabody by Severn Teackle Wallis, 1870. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Address Delivered before the Society of the Alumni of the Virginia Military Institute, July 4th 1871 by John M. Patton, 1873. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Constitution of the State of Virginia, 1874. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Virginia: A Geographical and Political Summary, Board of Immigration, 1876. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Lawyers' Combined Note adn Memorandum Book, and Manual of the Principles of Law and Equity prepared by Edward C. Carrington, Campbell Carrington, and Irving Williamson, 1876. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Richmond College Messenger, volume 6, number 9, 1881. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Richmond College Messenger, volume 7, number 2 (2 copies), 1881. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Charter of the Richmond, Fredericksburg, and Potomac Railroad Company, and other Acts in Relation to Said Company, 1881. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Richmond College Messenger, volume 7, number 4, 1882. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Richmond College Messenger, volume 8, number 2, 1882. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Richmond College Messenger, volume 8, number 6, 1882. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Early Years of the University of Virginia: Address of H. Tutwiler, A.M., LL.D., of Alabama, before the Alumni Society of the University of Virginia, Thursday, June 29th, 1882, 1882. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - MacMillan's Magazine, number 329, March 1887. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - The Charter, Organization, and By-laws of the Merchants Bank of Danville, Va., 1888. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Report on the Public Debt of Virginia to the Senate by Bradley T. Johnson, 1889. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Robert Edward Lee. An Address Delivered at the Dedication of the Monument to General Robert Edward Lee at Richmond, Virginia, May 29, 1890 by Archer Anderson, 1890. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - An Engineering Problem at Richmond, Va." by W. H. Adams, 1890. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Montague & Massie, Attorneys-at-law, business card, ca. 1890-1896. (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Discharge witness slips with Montague's stamped signature, ca. 1890s. (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Souvenir of the Unveiling of the Monument to Mary, the Mother of Washington. Fredericksburg, Virginia, May 10, 1894, (2 copies), 1894. (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Address to the Republicans of the Sixth District of Virginia. How J. Hampton Hoge was not Nominated, by C. A. Heermans, 1894. (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Speech of Hon. John G. Carlisle, at Memphis, Tenn.,1895. (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - What the South Is Doing for Education and What Education Is Doing for the South by W. T. Harris, 1895. (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - The Public Debt. Extract from Virginia Annual Reports, 1894,[1895]. (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Statement of the Attorney-General concerning the Right of the President to Enforce Federal Authority in all Parts of the Union and Mr. Bryan's Position with Relation Thereto,1896. (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Inaugural Address of His Excellency J. Hoge Tyler before the General Assembly of Virginia,1 January 1898. (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Congressional Record, Fifty-Fifth Congress, Second Session, 1898. (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - The Society of the Colonial Dames of America in the State of Virginia,1898. (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Wall Street Promoters, by J. M. Mason, 1899. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Improvement of James River, Virginia. Its Value to Commerce and Necessity as a Work of Both National and Local Importance, by Joint Committee representing the City Council of Richmond and the Richmond Chamber of Commerce, (2 copies), 1899. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - The Society of the Colonial Dames of America in the State of Virginia, (2 copies) 1899. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Democratic State Organization Adopted at the State Convention at Norfolk, Virginia, (3 copies) 3 May 1900. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - The Development of the District of Columbia by Henry B. F. Macfarland 1900. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - First Annual Report of the Virginia State Legislative Board1900. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - The Preservation of the Past. An Address Delivered before the Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities by Charles W. Kent, 14 March 1901. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Hon. Claude A. Swanson: A Candidate for the Democratic Nomination for Governor of Virginia at the Convention to be Held at Norfolk, Virginia,1901. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Republican Platform Adopted at Roanoke, Va.,August 1901. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Platform Adopted at Norfolk, (2 copies) August 1901. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Hon. Carter Glass's Speech Delivered before the Constitutional Convention, (3 copies) 5 September 1901. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Minority Report of J. C. Wysor, One of the Committee on Elective Franchise, Qualification for Office, etc.,1901. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Democratic State Organization. Adopted at the State Convention at Norfolk, Virginia, May 3, 1900,1901. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Bulletins of the University of Virginia, volume 1, number 4 (new series), October 1901. (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Suffrage Clauses of the Constitutions of the States of the American Union, together with the Provisions Respecting Suffrage Contained in the Constitution of the United States, and the Acts of Congress for the Government of the Territories or Districts of the United States, 1901. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Report of the Committee on the Elective Franchise, Qualification for Office, Basis of Representation and Apportionment, and on Elections,1901. (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Report of a Minority of the Committee on the Elective Franchise, Qualification for Office, Basis of Representation and Apportionment, and on Elections,1901. (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - White Men!!! Read and Consider--Then Vote,1901. (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - The Platforms of 1901. Examine, Compare, adn Make Your Choice,1901. (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Political Crimes and Their Consequences, by Algernon Sidney Crapsey, 1901. (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - For the purpose of giving effect to the Resolution adopted by the Convention of the Democratic Party at Norfolk...,1902. (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Inaugural Address of Hon. A. J. Montague, Delivered January 1st 1902, before the Constitutional Convention, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Congressional Record, Fifty-seventh Congress, First Session, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Message of the Governor of Virginia to the General Assembly,20 February 1902. (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Baccalaureate Address before the University of Georgia, by Edward M. Shepard (3 copies), 18 June 1902. (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Bulletins of the University of Virginia, volume 2, number 3 (new series), July 1902. (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Educational Journal, September 1902. (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Speech Delivered by Edward M. Shepard before the Jeffersonian Association of St. Louis, Mo., (6 copies), 10 October 1902. (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - University of Virginia Magazine, volume 46, number 1, November 1902. (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Forefathers' Day: New England Society fo Pennsylvania, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Regulations for the Uniform of the United States Army, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Facts About the South by Richard H. Edmonds, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Part First of Virginia School Report. For Years 1899-1900 and 1900-1901, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - The Constitution of the State of Virginia, Adopted by the Convention of 1901-2, 1902. (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Southern Education Notes, series I, number 23, 10 January 1903. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Jefferson Davis, address by William Hepburn Russell, 1903. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Hello Bill, volume 5, number 1, January 1903. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - General Orders number 25, Headquarters of the Army,10 March 1903. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - General Orders number 29, Headquarters of the Army,12 March 1903. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Modern Power of World Public Opinion address by Edward M. Shepard at Tulane University, 1903. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - The Outlook, volume 73, number 11, 14 March 1903. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - General Orders number 36, Headquareters of the Army21 March 1903. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - The Educational and Industrial Emancipation of the Negro, by Booker T. Washington, 1903. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - General Orders number 54, Headquarters of the Army,10 April 1903. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - General Orders, number 62, Headquarters of the Army,28 April 1903. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Southern Education, volume 1, numbers 8 and 9, 7 May 1903. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - General Orders, number 70, Headquarters of the Army,13 May 1903. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - General Orders, number 94, Headquarters of the Army,26 June 1903. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Alkahest Magazine, 7th year, number 10, July 1903. (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - General Orders, number 37, War Department,16 October 1903. (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Bulletins of the University of Virginia, volume 3, number 4 (new series), October 1903. (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Remarks of Hon. Francis G. Newlands, of Nevada, in the Senate of the United States,1903. (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - The Problem in the South by Charles W. Dabney, 1903. (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Circular Number 2--Corporations. Methods adn Costs of Obtaining Charters in Virginia, Commonwealth of Virginia, State Corporation Commission, 1903. (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - The United States a Commerical World Power Address Delivered at the Annual Banquet of the Chamber of Commerce of Rochester, N.Y. by Charles R. Flint, 1904. (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - The Work and Influence of Hampton: Proceedings of a Meeting held in New York City,1904. (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Card for the launching of the battleship Virginia, 5 April 1904. (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Envelope addressed to Governor Montague from W. H. Buckler, 1904. (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Democratic National Convention Delegate's Ticket, 6 July 1904. (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - The Outlook, volume 78, number 7, 15 October 1904. (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - The Outlook, volume 78, number 11, 12 November 1904. (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Tearsheet endorsement of Hayner Whiskey by Senator Thomas S. Martin from The Wide World, December 1904. (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - The Republican Party: A Party fit to govern, by John Hay and Elihu Root, 1904. (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - The Second American Conference on International Arbitration Held in Washington, D.C., 1904. (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Democracy's Leaders. Alton Brooks Parker,1904. (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - A Trip to Tariffland in Mrs. Workman's Clothes Press,1904. (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Congressional Record, Fifty-Eighth Congress, Third Session, 1905. (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Co-Operative Legislative Board of Railroad Employees of Virginia,1905. (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Congressional Record, Speech of Hon. Thos. S. Martin, of Virginia in the Senate of the United States,17 February 1905. (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Resolution number 294 in the Senate of the United States,28 February 1905. (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Tearsheet endorsement of Hayner Whiskey by Senator Thomas S. Martin from Ainslee's Advertiser, February 1905. (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Printed letter, from C. V. Meredith, Richmond, Virginia, to W. I. Steele, Charlottesville, Virginia--campaign literature (2 copies), 12 May 1905. (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - A Fable of the Martin and the Woodpecker and A Fable of the Eagle, the Martin, and the Woodpecker, (6 copies), 25 May 1905. (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - The John P. Branch Historical Papers of Randolph-Macon College, volume II, number 1, June 1905. (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Plan of Legalized Democratic Primary,1905. (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Resolutions of the Board of Directors of the Richmond Chamber of Commerce. Report of its Committee on Inland Trade and of Outward Trade Acting Jointly and a Communication to the News-Leader Relating to the Purchase of the Richmodn Dock by the City of Richmond,1905. (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - The Christ of the Andes: the Story of the Erection of the Great Peace Monument on the Andean Boundary Between Chile and Argentina,1905. (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Public School Officials of Virginia,1905. (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - In 1882 a Republican Board of Education adopted...,[1905]. (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - Fire Alarms issued by S. t. Pulliam and Company, [1905]. (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - What Kind of Language Study Aids in teh Mastery of Natural Science? by W. T. Harris (2 copies), 1906. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - The Messenger, volume XXXII, number 5, February 2006. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Colombia: A Land of Great Possibilities by John Barrett, 1906. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Program: Twenty-second Annual Meeting of the West Virginia Bar Association, Thursday and Friday December 27th and 28th, 1906, (2 copies) 1906. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Regulation of Railroad Rages: Speech of Hon. Joseph W. Bailey, of Texas, in the Senate of the United States, 1906. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Addresses, Messages and Proclamations of Andrew Jackson Montague, Governor of Virginia, 1902-1906, (2 copies) 1906. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Addresses, Messages and Proclamations of Andrew Jackson Montague, Governor of Virginia, 1902-'06, 1906. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Speeches Incident to the Visit of Secretary Root to South America July 4 to September 30 19061906. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - American Constitutions: A Compilation of the Political Constitutions of the Independent Nations of the New World by José Ignacio Rodriguez, 1906. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Safe Deposit and Trust Corporation, notebook, 1906. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Jamestown, Virginia, (2 copies). (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Delegation Pan-Am. Conference, tag (2 tags), 1906. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Pan American Conference U.S. Delegation, sheets (6 copies), 1906. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Ticket to a University Club dinner in honor of A. J. Montague, 15 December 1906. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Flyer advertising a talk, A Community Worth Living In, by A. J. Montague at the Academy of Music, 1907. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - The Outlook for the South by Harry Wise, from The Tradesman, 15 June 1907. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Report of the Delegates of the United States to the Third International American Conference, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, July-August 1906, 1907. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Law class Schedule, 1907-8 Richmond College Law School,1907. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - A Railroad Defense of the Roosevelt Policies, in The Literary Digest, volume XXXVI, number 1, 4 January 1908. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Topics of the Day: Mr. Taft's Boston Speech, in The Literary Digest, volume XXXVI, number 2, 11 January 1908. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - The Sociology of Political Parties by Lester F. Ward in American Journal of Sociology, volume XIII, number 4, January 1908. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - By-laws of ACCA Temple A.A.O.N.M.S., 1908. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - The John P. Branch Historical Papers of Randolph-Macon College, volume II, numbers 3 and 4, June 1908. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - If our protective system... by Clyde H. Tavenner, 1908. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Envelope from the Law Offices of Montague and Montague, 1908. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - List of Cabin Passengers [on the] Twin-Screw Express S.S.Deutschland, Captain C. Kaempff,1909. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - List of Saloon Passengers, R.M.S. Mauretania, from Liverpool, Saturday, October 23rd, 1909, for New York, via Queenstown,1909. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Address of Mr. A. J. Montague, of Richmond, Va., reprinted from The Proceedings of the American Society of International Law, 1909. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Table of Foreign Moneys showing Approximate Value in Dollars,1910. (Box 52, Folder 11)